Teacher
Teacher Danni
Teacher Danni, something's wrong!
Xiao Qi is planning on selling a kidney!
What?
I'll bring him back.
Wait for me here.
I'm coming with you.
Stay here and wait for me.
I'll bring him back safely.
But I...
Don't worry.
Brother Qiang.
Need some help?
I'll handle my own business.
You be careful out there!
Who let you in here?
Who the hell are you?
Hey, boss, boss!
Wait a sec.
He signed the contract himself.
He's the one who insisted on selling a kidney.
He needed the money.
It's none of my business.
I just run a business.
I'm young and naive.
Take care, I won't see you out.
Thanks for letting me off!
Who forced you into selling a kidney?
I...
My sister...
What happened to A Fen?
She's with Elephant.
She's being held at the nightclub.
Money.
I need money.
With money, I can save my sister.
Don't be afraid. Take your time.
What happened?
To save up for Dad's medical bills,
she borrowed from a loan shark.
Compound interest just kept piling up.
Why do you look like you've seen a ghost?
Brother...
Just give me two more days.
I promise, within two days,
I'll pay back every cent.
You borrow, you pay.
That's the rule.
Your dad's that sick,
and I only came collecting today.
That's me being mighty decent, right?
But...
But I've already...
I've already paid back so much.
How much have you actually paid?
You should know deep down.
You signed the contract yourself.
And now you wanna weasel out?
Don't!
Why so tense?
You really care about these plates, huh?
Don't!
Brother...
Brother, I'm begging you.
Stop smashing them.
Really, if you break them, I have to pay.
Brother, stop smashing them.
Stop smashing them.
Why are you working yourself up so much?
What for?
We all understand your dad's situation.
We're all human.
Giving you a few more days isn't impossible.
Really?
Thank you, thank you, Brother.
Thank you.
Here's the deal.
Thank you, thank you.
I'll take you to meet my boss.
If you keep him happy,
he might just wipe your debt clean.
No.
I won't go.
Don't break them!
Brother...
I'm sorry.
Brother, I'm begging you.
I beg you, tell them to stop smashing.
I have to pay for whatever gets broken.
Brother, stop, stop smashing.
I...
I'll go with you, I'll go.
Move.
Come on, move.
Get moving.
What are you doing, Loan Shark King?
This ain't right.
Be gentle with her.
I didn't mean to, boss.
I just don't know my own strength.
A Fen, right?
You're quite pretty.
You're even prettier than your photo.
Come here.
Did you get hurt?
Dragged back, huh.
Let me rub some medicinal wine on you.
Come, come.
Sit here.
How did you end up like this?
In so much debt.
The interest on this is brutal, you know.
Brother Elephant.
Brother Elephant, Brother Elephant.
I'll work hard to pay you back.
Work hard, keep pushing.
Delivering goods and washing dishes,
just to make a few hundred a day.
Working yourself to the bone.
What's the point?
Look at your hands.
They're all blistered.
Does it hurt?
Let me tell you,
You'll never pay it off like this.
Why not stay with me?
I love your type the most,
an inexperienced virgin.
Brother Elephant, I don't do that kind of thing.
Do you want your dad to run out of meds,
or your brother selling a kidney?
Here's the deal.
You spend one night with me,
make me nice and comfortable,
and we can easily settle your debt.
Exactly.
We're all adults here.
One big happy family,
Your whole family will be blessed.
Brother, have a drink.
Made up your mind?
Get over here.
On your knees.
After this,
my whole debt really gets wiped clean?
Of course.
I, Brother Elephant, always keep my word.
Work hard, keep pushing.
What are you crying for?
Weren't you just fine a moment ago?
Everything I was supposed to do,
I've done it all.
So my debt to you is wiped clean.
Sure.
I, Elephant, am a man of my word.
The money I lent you is wiped clean.
But the interest, of course,
still has to be paid.
You've had it for so long,
it adds up to quite a sum.
I'll have them do the math,
and tell you the number tomorrow.
That's not what you said just now.
What I said from start to finish was:
the money I lent you is wiped clean.
Who do you think you are?
Millions for one night in bed?
Are you made of gold?
Say that again.
Who do you think you are?
Why did you lie to me?
That's not what you said just now.
Get away from me!
What's with all the crying?
You're a woman, after all.
Making money is easy for you, isn't it?
You've got the body,
and the looks.
And I just tried out your skills,
and they're not bad at all.
Get lost!
You don't want your dad running out of meds,
and you want to pay off the debt soon.
I understand your devotion to your father.
Why not stay here and work for me?
You won't have to lift a finger all day.
Just be a good girl,
and men will line up to throw money at you.
Right?
Pay off your debt and have some fun too.
Think about it.
Remember to clock in on time tomorrow!
Sis, I'm home.
How was your day
at school?
It was fine.
Sis.
Here, drink some water.
I brought back some roast chicken from work.
We're eating well tonight.
Xiao Qi, how many times have I told you?
I mean it,
stop working at those places.
I can handle all this.
Do you not understand?
It's fine. I can manage.
Don't worry, Sis.
My pay from the flower shop and the club
is coming through soon.
I did the math,
and it should cover Dad's next round of chemo.
Sis, you work way too hard.
I have to help share the load.
Once I graduate,
I can find a real job.
By then,
we won't have to work so hard.